(Leonard:)No.
(Bernadette:)I have one.
(Bernadette:)What if you got
a giant slingshot
(Bernadette:)and flung yourself
into the wall?
(Howard:)Is that supposed
to be funny?
(Raj:)Hold on.
(Raj:)Yeah, that's funny.
- All right, we're heading out.
- Mm-hmm.
(Amy:)I'll call you when
we get to the hotel.
(Sheldon:)And if they have any of those
tiny bottles of shampoo?
(Amy:)I will bring them home
so you can show me
(Amy:)how Godzilla takes a shower.
(Leonard:)Have fun.
Thanks.
(Penny:)Are you ready?
(Amy:)Uh-huh.
(Amy:)Bye, Sheldon.
(Penny:)You know what?
(Sheldon:)I feel uncomfortable engaging
in a public display of affection
(Sheldon:)while their relationship
is strained.
(Leonard:)Go ahead, it's fine.
(Amy:)Bye.
Bye.